# **BRAD RICHARDSON**

SR. USER INTERFACE DEVELOPER

#### PROFIL F

#### Name

**Brad Richardson** 

#### **Address**

527 Suttalee Lane Irmo, SC 29063

#### **Phone**

(843) 617-2754

#### **Email**

brad@designchanged.us

#### Website

designchanged.us

### SOCIAL

facebook.com/bradwrichardson twitter.com/bradrich48 linkedin.com/in/bradwrichardson github.com/bradrich

#### PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Part Strategist, Part Developer and Part Designer. User Interface Strategist and Designer with a passion for beautiful design and functional, simplistic user experiences. Front-End Developer who focuses on writing clean and elegant code that validates using today's standards and displays properly no matter what the user's

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Present Advance America

Sr. UI Developer

Responsible for the Design and Development of Advance America's online suite of financial applications. Design includes building graphics, color schemes and layouts of the User Interface for applications being utilized throughout the company. Development includes writing semantic code that adheres to all industry standards and best practices. Languages being used are HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, XML and AngularJS. Every project is developed within the Agile SCRUM development process.

### Present Changed

Founder

Changed is your go-to solution for Marketing, Design and Customer Service Service Strategy situations. It is my responsibility to oversee all aspects of Changed. My knowledge of interactive marketing, print and website design, and business consulting allows Changed to offer a vast array of services for small to medium-sized businesses.

#### 2012 - 2013 HillSouth

Chief Development Officer

As the Chief Development Officer at HillSouth, it was my responsibility to oversee the relationship advancements of HillSouth. I find and procure vendors, business partnerships and new customer verticals and drive business growth.

#### 2008 - 2012 HillSouth

**Chief Creative Officer** 

As the Chief Creative Officer for HillSouth, I was responsible for the design, functionality and deployment of websites and other marketing pieces

for our clients.

## **BRAD RICHARDSON**

SR. USER INTERFACE DEVELOPER

device size is. Back-End

Developer that concentrates on content management systems, mainly Umbraco, giving each and every client the best experience in keeping their websites up-to-date. I am looking forward to continuing my career and learning new and better skills from amazing colleagues. I am looking forward to starting new projects and doing everything in my power to assist in already established projects.

2006 - 2008 HillSouth

Internet Solutions Architect

I was responsible for creating, building and implementing website and internet application designs for a diverse group of clients. It was my responsibility to learn the client's organization, meet the people that made that organization tick, learn the target audience and their core needs and finally to provide them all with the best in design.

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATIONS

2002 - 2006 BA Graphic Design / CS Minor

Francis Marion University

Dec. 5, 2013 Certified ScrumMaster

ScrumAlliance

## SKILLS

Professional		Personal	
JavaScript	>>>>>>>	Organization	>>>>>>>
HTML / CSS	>>>>>>>	Communication	>>>>>>>
Git	>>>>>>>	Time Keeping	>>>>>>>
SSH / ZSH	>>>>>>>	Commitment	>>>>>>
PS / Sketch	>>>>>>>	Hardworking	>>>>>>

#### **REFERENCES**

**Coleman Simons** 

(609) 335-2393 colejsimons@gmail.com

Andy Patel (843) 687-9236 andy@hillsouth.com

Robert "Bob" Mills (803) 446-5124 millsrd001@gmail.com